North East Organization for Nursing (NEON) Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
North East Organization for Nursing (NEON) Records.
1968-1995.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
North East Organization for Nursing
2.5 linear feet
MSS19970130
Official records of the major New England regional nursing association.
History
Scope and Content
The collection contains minutes, correspondence, publications, and meeting materials of the organization.
Arrangement
Series I: Records (unprocessed) ( 1968-1995 )
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to nursing in Connecticut. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Notebooks.; Publications.; Photographs.; Blueprints.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.
Occupations:
Professional organization.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Detailed Description
- Series I: Records, 1968-1995
  - Minutes, 1986 May 13 - 1990 January 11 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1990-1995 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Current Members, 1995 (Box 2:, Folder 1)
  - Executive Boards, 1994-1995 (Box 2:, Folder 2)
  - News, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 3)
  - By-laws, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder 4)
  - By-laws, 1991 October (Box 2:, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Plan and Mission Statement, 1990 October 4 (Box 2:, Folder 6)
  - MARNA-Dissolution Merger, 1995 January 11 (Box 2:, Folder 7)
  - MARNA- Bylaws, 1968, 1988 (Box 2:, Folder 8)
  - FY Bills Paid, 1993 (Box 2:, Folder 9)
  - Spring Meetings, 1992 April 2 (Box 2:, Folder 10)
  - Program-Fall, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder 11)
  - Meeting-Spring, 1993 (Box 2:, Folder 12)
  - Fall Conference, 1993 (Box 2:, Folder 13)
  - Fall Conference, 1994 (Box 2:, Folder 14)
  - Conference-Archival, 1995 (Box 2:, Folder 15)
  - Project, 1984-1991 (Box 2:, Folder 16)
  - Fleet Payroll Info., 1991 January 31, 1992 January 13 (Box 2:, Folder 17)
  - Conference Expenses, 1991 April (Box 2:, Folder 18)
  - Fall Conference Expenses, 1991 (Box 2:, Folder 19)
  - Receipts-Expenses Pre-Fy, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder 20)
  - Checking, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder 21)
  - Fy-Bills Paid, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder 22)
  - Conference Expenses: Fall, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder 23)
  - Bank Statements, 1989-1992 (Box 2:, Folder 24)
  - Canceled Checks Statement, 1993-1994 (Box 2:, Folder 25)
  - Substance Abuse, 1992 April 2 - 4 (Box 2:, Folder 26)
  - Program Conference, 1992 October (Box 2:, Folder 27)
  - Spring Meetings, 1991 April 4 (Box 2:, Folder 28)
  - Conference, 1990 October 4 (Box 2:, Folder 29)
  - Spring Program, 1990 (Box 2:, Folder 30)
  - Conference: Fall, 1989 (Box 2:, Folder 31)
  - Spring Conference, 1989 April (Box 2:, Folder 32)
  - Meeting, 1988 October 6 (Box 2:, Folder 33)
  - Fall Meeting, 1987 (Box 2:, Folder 34)
  - Spring Meeting, 1987 (Box 2:, Folder 35)
  - Fall Meeting, 1986 (Box 2:, Folder 36)
  - Spring Meeting, 1986 (Box 2:, Folder 37)
  - Fall Meeting, 1985 (Box 2:, Folder 38)
  - Fall Meeting, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 39)
  - EDC Files: Correspondence, 1983 January 24 (Box 2:, Folder 40)
  - Memebership&Conference Brochures (Box 2:, Folder 41)
  - NECHEN/NEBHE News, 1978-1980 (Box 2:, Folder 42)
  - Retreat-Providence, 1995 June 22 - 23 (Box 2:, Folder 43)
  - Beginnings (excerpts), 1981 March 27 - 1991 April 4 (Box 2:, Folder 44)
  - NECHEN/NEBHE, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 45)
  - NECHEN/NEBHE, 1980-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 46)
  - Spring Program, 1986 (Box 2:, Folder 47)
  - Fall Conference&Anuual Meeting, 1994 (Box 2:, Folder 48)
  - Newsletter, 1984, 1989, 1990-1995 (Box 2:, Folder 49)